Is it going well, me?
Indeed. Exactly as planned.
I heard from me #193...
...and me #238 not long ago.
There's no time to dilly-dally.
It's about time for the next step.
Then let's get moving.
Let us meet again soon...
On the path to Hades.
In Hell on Earth.
Hmm? Something wrong?
No, but what a cute lunch that is.
You want a bite?
I'd feel guilty if I didn't share, too.
Would you take some of mine as a trade?
Oh? What are they doing?
A battle's taking place.
Two pros are facing off,
just like in manga!
Insight. I think I see their auras.
Here. Help yourself.
"Meow"
Hmm? Having trouble deciding?
I-I'll take this one.
Th-That's Shido for you.
It's super delicious.
Really? I'm glad you like it.
Now it's my turn. Say "Ah!"
Ahh!
What do you think, Shido?
Yeah, it's delicious.
I'm always the one making the food.
I haven't had anyone else's
home cooking in forever!
My, my. You exaggerate.
Care for another?
Do try my egg omelet.
Ooh! I don't get it, but I'm impressed!
Tohka, stand back. It's dangerous.
Grr! How dare they show off without us!
Agreement. We want to compete, too.
These bonito flakes!
This is no ordinary soy sauce!
Same here. There's seaweed in it.
And tuna, too!
Could I interest you in some of this?
Wh-What the--?!
Hot... miso soup?!
Shall we chalk this up as another tie?
For sure.
--Whoa!
Oh? Could you hold still for me?
Wh-What?
Say, Shido...
Do you have any plans
after school next Wednesday?
Wednesday? Sorry, but I'm
doing something I can't miss:
Oh?
Going on a date with the girl
in front of me, that is.
Oh my. My, my. I see we have
the same thing in mind.
Thanks for your time in advance.
Of course. But you don't mean
"Thanks for your time" in the normal way.
What a funny thing to say.
You can interpret it
the standard way, if you please.
However, when it comes to
the day in question...
I plan to do exactly what you're thinking.
I'm looking forward to it, Shido.
You okay, Shido?
Yeah, more or less.
That went well. Kurumi's levels
had some swings there.
Really?
Though, a certain someone's
levels swung just as much.
Erk!
Hey, why did Kurumi pick next Wednesday?
Is there something then?
Next Wednesday...
"Holidays: Valentine's Day"
You get chocolate from people
that like you?! Wow, what a fun day!
Well, you're right about that,
but you're on the giving side.
Hmm? Oh...
That's okay. I'm happy
to give Shido something...
You're clearly disappointed.
Kurumi plans to win their battle
with a Valentine's date.
And if Darling loses,
she'll take his Spirit power and life.
I doubt Shido will admit defeat
if doing so costs his life.
Kurumi wouldn't challenge him
unless she thought she could win.
We have two plays here: One is for
all of us to give him chocolate, too.
Drown her out, huh?
True... If I was a guy and only got
chocolate from Kurumin,
I'd fall for her.
Wise plan, but I was
giving him some anyway.
So, the other play we have is...
Origami? Or Miku, or Nia?
--That's Shido for you.
--Nice guess!
Given your choices, it's no surprise!
May I, Shido? Just relax.
That's right. We girls
will take care of you.
Yeah, yeah. With some experience,
Kurumi's nothing to be afraid of!
--Good grief!
--Whoa!
Whatever you're up to,
go back to your rooms!
--Aww, that's no fun!
--I knew it wouldn't work.
Jeez! What the heck?
Who is it now? Don't tell me... Kurumi?!
Wh-What?
Oh? That's Shido Itsuka?
Looks pretty normal to me.
Yeah? I think he's cute!
Paper?
Boo!
You're DEM's thing...!
Oh? You know us?
Calling us "DEM's thing" is so rude.
Yeah! We're proper Spirits, too!
We're called Nibeelcole.
Cool name, right?
But since Father made us,
we're different than the Spirits you know.
Spirits? Father? Made you?
Confused?
We could explain,
but it's pointless. Because...
...you're gonna die anyway.
Oh? Camael's regeneration, huh?
That's gonna make this annoying.
It's no fair if you can't die.
Whatever. We'll just
kill him till he does.
Huh?
Morning, Kotori.
Koto... ri?!
What are you staring at?
The bare legs of your Big Sis, perhaps?
You're a guy, after all.
B-Big Sis?! You're Kotori... right?
You've gotta be. But what are those?
Huh? "Those"?
Even if you had a growth spurt,
that doesn't explain those boob--
Shido.
Wha--?!
Shido, Mom needs you to taste test.
By the way, I'm Dad.
Um... Could you help me, Son?
I mean... sweetie?
Shido! I mean... Itsuka!
It's time for Health Ed. class.
You see, a stamen and a pistil...
Morning, Shido.
Too bad you weren't here
when I didn't have a towel.
Or did you come to take it off
yourself, you bad boy?
Oho, do you have a boo-boo?
Where does it hurt?
Point. Even as an adult,
you talk like a child.
Hmm. Are you awake, Mister?
Huh? Huh?
"We tried to get a head start"
We failed, but refuse to give up.
Who said a little girl can't be a big sis?
Grr! Why were we made small?!
I wanna help Darling out, too!
With us for contrast,
it's easier to see their "assets."
Wh-What is all this?
It's training.
Training?
Yes.
To ensure you don't fall victim
to Kurumi Tokisaki's sexiness.
To better resist Kurumi, you need to get
used to a mature girl's charms.
Ah... You used Natsumi's
Haniel to transform?
Well then, let's resume the training.
Itsuka! You're late for
Tohka-sensei's Naughty Class!
Don't be shy! You can touch 'em!
Mister, come spend
an indulgent night with Muku.
Argh, jeez! I can't take this!
Where are you going, Itsuka?!
Class is in session!
Eh?
Reine?
Oh... There, there.
"Baking Chocolate"
Let's move on to the next plan.
Reine got these ingredients for us.
If you don't know what to do,
ask me or Reine.
Hmm... So many ingredients
to choose from.
Sister, what's the difference between
these light and dark colors?
Huh? Um, well...
The milk to cocoa ratio.
Basically, darker means it's more bitter,
and lighter means its sweeter.
Oho, I see.
I learned something.
Thanks, Reine.
What kind of chocolate will you make?
Hmm... Just melting it
into a shape feels so uninspired.
Though, if it's too involved,
I might mess up.
You're probably worrying over nothing.
Think of who you're giving it to.
Will they disapprove of something
you made just because it's simple?
You're right--I'm overthinking things.
Kotori, Reine!
I want to make chocolate
that I can drizzle over my body!
I wanna make him some
super-energy-boost bars!
What should go in it? Softshell--
Make normal chocolate!
What's this?
Silicone for a mold case.
A mold of what?
Me.
I see. But there's just
one problem with that:
Problem?
Think how much volume
there is in a human body.
Shin would consume
an excessive amount of sugar.
I didn't consider that.
How embarrassing.
You're too busy thinking about Shin.
Next time, keep his health in mind.
All right. I'll size it down
while maintaining the quality.
Sorry to drag you into this
on your day off, Reine.
Um, I've always wondered, Reine:
Why do you refer to Shido as Shin?
At first, I thought his name was Shintaro.
I've kept calling him that ever since.
Ah, so that's why...
Now then, I suppose I should get
started on mine, too.
You? Huh? Who for?
Well, the Fraxinus crew, my colleagues
at Raizen High, and Shin, too.
Aww! I thought maybe
you found someone special!
Sorry to disappoint you,
but there's no one like that these days.
Confirmation. You said, "these days."
Oh, yeah? So there was someone
you liked in the past?
--Really?
--Are you serious?
--For real?
Mm, there was. Just one.
--Ooh!
I'm shocked. What were they like?
If it's someone Reine liked,
I bet they were lovely.
Yes, he was very kind.
Such a kind person.
I doubt that anyone--past or future--
can surpass his place in my heart.
He was my first love...
and will be my last love.
What a beautiful story, Ms. Murasame.
I almost envy you.
Kurumi!
So, this is where you live?
Isn't it just lovely?
To be honest, I was planning to give
Shido some chocolate, too.
If you don't mind, may I join you?
Sure, you can join us.
Agreed. It's a good chance to get
data on her. I'll return to Fraxinus.
Yeah, please do.
Well, since I have permission,
I'll get started right away.
Shido's heart shall be mine.
Not happening! I'll protect Shido!
I-I'll do my best!
It won't go your way!
I won't lose so easily.
"Baking Chocolate"
"Hokkaido Fresh Cream"
So, Kotori... How do I start?
Kotori? How do you melt chocolate?
Huh? Uh, well...
Oh, my, Kotori. Is it your first time
tempering chocolate?
O-Of course, I've done it before!
Tempering...?
Temper... ing...
Temper... Tenpa!
Huh? Wh-What?
Uh, it's nothing!
Melting chocolate is as easy as this!
Stop the heat!
Just take the pot off!
Hot!
My, my.
O-Origami, you know how
to make chocolate, don't you?
What?
Um, Kotori?
What?!
Um, well... I'm not super confident,
but I think I know the basics.
My savior!
--Happy Valentine's!
Thanks, everyone! I've never gotten
this much chocolate!
Mister, don't lose to that girl!
They give you more at school.
Eat our chocolate
and do your best, Shido!
Right!
Now then, what comes next?
Next is our turn.
Ah, yes. Godspeed.
To a good death.
To a meaningful demise.
For my sake.
And my sake.
And... Shido's sake.
"Episode 10:
'Girl Time.'"
Long ago, Kurumi Tokisaki
was a normal human.
Why did she end up as "The Worst Spirit"?
Next time: "Past Sins."
"Episode 11: 'Past Sins.'"
Kurumi's past is unfolded.